<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="23" uniqueCount="23"><si><t>id</t></si><si><t>gt</t></si><si><t>parsed_output</t></si><si><t>Patient</t></si><si><t>Study</t></si><si><t>&gt; No obvious midline shifting or intracerebral hemorrhage can be found in this exam.
&gt; Mild generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci, cerebellar fissures and ventricular system.
&gt; Mild nonspecific low density patches at bilateral periventricular white matter without mass effect.
R/I small vascular ischemic disease.
&gt; No remarkable finding of paranasal sinuses and bilateral mastoids.
&gt; Grossly intact visible bony structures.
&gt; Early infarction could be underdetected by CT.
Suggest clinical correlation.
Conclusion
Senile change.</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_15456</t></si><si><t>&gt; Presence of thin-layered SDH at right occipital region about 2.8 mm in thickness.
&gt; Low dense subdural effusion at left fronto-parietal region, with mass effect to left lateral ventricle and minimal midline shift.
&gt; Old lacunar infarction at right thalamus.
&gt; Mild generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci, cerebellar fissures and ventricular system.
&gt; Calcification at the wall of left intracranial vertebral artery and the cavernous part of bilateral internal carotid arteries.
&gt; No remarkable finding of paranasal sinuses and bilateral mastoids.
&gt; Grossly intact visible bony structures.
Impression
Low dense subdural effusion at left fronto-parietal region, with mass effect to left lateral ventricle and minimal midline shift.</t></si><si><t>&gt; Generalized atrophic change of the brain parenchyma with widening of sulci and dilated ventricular system.
&gt; No obvious midline shifting or intracerebral hemorrhage can be found in this exam.
&gt; Old cerebrovascular accident with Encephalomalacia in the right cerebellar hemisphere.
&gt; Several lacunar infarcts in the right lentiform nucleus.</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_15876</t></si><si><t>&gt; Post-operative change with bone defects in left frontotemporoparietal skull, tissue loss in left anterior temporal, frontal pole and frontal opercular region.
&gt; Chronic SDH with linear calcification at left high frontoparietal convexity about 1.0cm in thickness and left high frontotemporal convexity about 0.6cm in thickness.
&gt; Minimal SDH noted at right low frontal convexity about 0.3cm in thickness.
&gt; No midline shift or brain herniation at current study.
&gt; Mild generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci, cerebellar fissures and ventricular system.
&gt; Mild nonspecific low density patches at bilateral periventricular white matter without mass effect.
R/I small vascular ischemic disease.
&gt; No remarkable finding of paranasal sinuses and bilateral mastoids.
&gt; Recommend clinical correlation and follow up.</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_16119</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_16203</t></si><si><t>&gt; No intracerebral hemorrhage, subdural hematoma, epidural hematoma, subarachnoid hemorrhage or midline shift seen in the current examination.
&gt; Generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci and ventricular system.
&gt; Extensive low density change is noted in the periventricular white matter of bilateral cerebral hemispheres, mostly likely angiopathic leukoencephalopathy from arteriosclerotic change.
&gt; Tiny low density lesions in bilateral lentiform nuclei, thalami and left corona radiata, compatible with lacunar infarctions.
&gt; Calcification in the wall of bilateral intracranial vertebral arteries and the cavernous part of bilateral internal carotid arteries.
CONCLUSION
aging process and atrophic change of the brain with lacunar infarctions in bilateral lentiform nuclei, thalami and left corona radiata; for more detailed information, please see the descriptions above.</t></si><si><t>&gt; Generalized atrophic change of the brain parenchyma with widening of sulci and dilated ventricular system.
&gt; Chronic subdural hematoma about 25mm in thickness in left frontoparietal region with mass effect, post-operative change with bone defect.
&gt; Slight midline shifting to the right side.</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_17451</t></si><si><t>eval_INS_17940</t></si><si><t>&gt; Nonspecific low density patches in bilateral periventricular white matter without mass effect.
R/I small vascular ischemic disease.
&gt; Mild generalized enlargement of cortical sulci, cerebellar fissures and ventricles, in favor of mild generalized brain atrophy.
&gt; No skull bone fracture.
Conclusions
SDH at left fronto-temporal about 10mm in thickness.</t></si><si><t>Findings
&gt; Moderate amount of subacute-chronic sdh along bilateral f-p-t convexities, about 13mm in maximal thickness.
this leads to buckling of bilateral cerebral hemispheres &gt; A small old insult at right frontal white matter.
&gt; A few hypodense lesions at bilateral basal ganglia, more in favor of old lacunar infarcts.
&gt; No midline shift nor brain herniation.
&gt; Atherosclerotic change of bilateral carotid siphons.
&gt; No hydrocephalus.
Conclusion
Moderate amount of subacute-chronic sdh along bilateral f-p-t convexities, about 13mm in maximal thickness.
This leads to buckling of bilateral cerebral hemispheres early infarction could be underdetected by ct.
Suggest clinical correlation.</t></si><si><t>&gt; Mild generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci and ventricular system.
&gt; White matter low density change is noted in the bilateral periventricular region, mostly likely angiopathic leukoencephalopathy from arteriosclerotic change.
&gt; Suspicious lacunar infarction at the left anterior basal ganglia.
&gt; No intracerebral hemorrhage and no midline shift is seen in the current examination.
&gt; Otherwise nothing remarkable.</t></si><si><t>Findings
&gt; Subacute sdh at left frontoparietal convexity, about 19mm in maximal thickness.
it caused buckling of left cerebral hemisphere, and midline shift to right side, 4mm.
&gt; Several old infarcts at right frontal, parietal, right anterior corona radiata, and bilateral cerebellums.
&gt; Atherosclerotic change of bilateral carotid siphons.
&gt; Skull bones appear intact without space-occupying lesion.
Conclusion
1.
Subacute SDH at left frontoparietal convexity, about 19mm in maximal thickness.
It caused buckling of left cerebral hemisphere, and midline shift to right side, 4mm.
2.
Several old infarcts.</t></si><si><t>&gt; No obvious midline shifting or intracerebral hemorrhage can be found in this exam.
&gt; Mild generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci, cerebellar fissures and ventricular system.
&gt; No remarkable finding of paranasal sinuses and bilateral mastoids.
&gt; Grossly intact visible bony structures.
&gt; Early infarction could be underdetected by CT.
Suggest clinical correlation.
Conclusion
Old small infarct in right cerebellar hemisphere and left occipital lobe.
Senile change.</t></si><si><t>&gt; No intracerebral hemorrhage, subdural hematoma, epidural hematoma, subarachnoid hemorrhage or midline shift seen in the current examination.
&gt; Tiny low density lesions in the anterior limb of right side internal capsule and corona radiata, compatible with old lacunar infarctions.
&gt; generalized loss of brain tissue with enlargement of cortical sulci and ventricular system.
&gt; Low density change is noted in the periventricular white matter of bilateral cerebral hemispheres, mostly likely angiopathic leukoencephalopathy from arteriosclerotic change.
&gt; Calcification in the wall of bilateral intracranial vertebral arteries and the cavernous part of bilateral ICAs.
Conclusion
Aging process and atrophic change of the brain with old lacunar infarctions in right corona radiata and anterior limb of right internal capsule; no ICH, SAH, SDH or EDH.</t></si></sst>